<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Internet Black Hole</title><link>/en/</link><description>Recent content on Internet Black Hole</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>(C) {year} {author}</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>(Almost) full Porteus disk encryption</title><link>/en/posts/almost-full-porteus-disk-encryption/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/posts/almost-full-porteus-disk-encryption/</guid><description>Disclaimer All data on target drive will be deleted! Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to backup important data to other disk if you have any. I&amp;rsquo;m not responsible for any damage nor loss of data on other disks resulting from careless use of the programs listed below or selecting the wrong drive or partition.
What we will need target USB stick or external drive Porteus ISO any Linux distro GRUB2 (syslinux, grub4dos, etc. aren&amp;rsquo;t suitable) cryptsetup fdisk or other partitioning tool some text editor cpio and xz disk format tools (fat32 and choose ext4 or xfs) root access a bit of time and knowledge In Porteus you can make GRUB module with command pmod -m grub and activate it.</description></item><item><title>Things have changed a bit</title><link>/en/posts/things-have-changed-a-bit/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 09:35:58 +0100</pubDate><guid>/en/posts/things-have-changed-a-bit/</guid><description>Some things have changed since last time I been in Warmerise, that is in December 2022. From the beginning, where I was here, this game was in 1000x600px frame. There was menu at the top, chat (removed), description under game (added hmm&amp;hellip; about 2 years ago?) and footer with copyright and links. Yesterday I came back here and I see that game fills whole page. I was even surprised that game menu showed quickly.</description></item><item><title>My first post</title><link>/en/posts/my-first-post/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/en/posts/my-first-post/</guid><description>This is my first post on my blog. I will write my posts first in Polish, and then I will try to translate them into English no longer than 2 days after writing the Polish version (there may be few exceptions of this). Of course, my English may not be very good and completely understandable, so if you find a sentence whose meaning is completely different from that in Polish or you simply don&amp;rsquo;t understand it, please write me about it.</description></item></channel></rss>